designtrends.com 2019-05-12

# Privacy Policy | DesignTrends

Privacy Policy | DesignTrends

This privacy policy describes how Designtrends.com uses and protects any information provided by the user while using the website.

Designtrends.com strives to ensure that user’s privacy is protected. Any information provided by the user shall be used only in accordance with the privacy statement.

Designtrends.com tends to change this policy from time to time by updating this page. User is responsible for checking this page every now and then and comply by the policies listed below.

  * We may collect information like Name, Email ID to provide better services to the user, like newsletters. We also periodically send mails about new products; offers or other information which we assume might be of interest to the user.
  * We may also contact the user for market research purposes, so that the website could be customised accordingly.
  * We are committed to ensuring that the user’s information is safe and secure. We have taken the necessary steps in terms of electronic or managerial procedures to secure the information.
  * We use cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps in providing analysis about web traffic. It also helps us improve our website and customise it according to the needs of the user. We strictly use this information for statistical analysis purposes, after which data is erased from the system.
  * Cookies are helpful to monitor the pages a user browses, and DO NOT provide access to a user’s computer or any information about the user.
  * Our website contains links to other websites. Once the user accesses these website by clicking on the link provided, we have no control over that website. We claim no responsibility for the protection and privacy of any information provided by the user while browsing those websites.
  * We will not sell, distribute or lease User’s personal information to third parties unless we have user’s permission or are required by law to do so.
